<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BeautifulTouristSpot</string>

    <string name="ran_title">RANGAMATI</string>
    <string name="ran_desc">
                            Sajek Valley is an emerging tourist spot in Bangladesh
                            situated among the hills of Kasalong range of mountains in Sajek union,
                            Baghaichhari Upazila in Rangamati District.
                            [1]The valley is 1800 feet above sea level.
                            [2]Sajek valley is known as the Queen of Hills and Roof of Rangamati.
    </string>
    <string name="ban_title">BANDARBAN</string>
    <string name="ban_desc">

                            Nilgiri, which literally means "Blue Mountain" in many languages, may refer to:
                            Nilgiri Biosphere Reserve, an International Biosphere Reserve in the Western Ghats and Nilgiri Hills ranges of South India
                            Nilgiri mountains, a range of mountains spanning the states of Tamil Nadu and Kerala in Southern India
                            Nilagiri or Nilgiri, a town in Balasore District of the state of Odisha in East India


    </string>
    <string name="saj_title">SAJEK</string>
    <string name="saj_desc">

      Rangamati (Bengali: রাঙামাটি, Chakma: ￼, Rangamattye) is a district in south-eastern Bangladesh.
      It is a part of the Chittagong Division[2]
      and the town of Rangamati serves as the headquarters of the district.
      Area-wise, Rangamati is the largest district of the country.

    </string>
    <string name="nil_title">NILGIRI</string>
    <string name="nil_desc">
                     Bandarban (Bengali: বান্দরবান) is a district in South-Eastern Bangladesh,
                     and a part of the Chittagong Division.
                    [1] It is one of the three hill districts of Bangladesh and a part of the Chittagong Hill Tracts,
                     the others being Rangamati District and Khagrachhari District.
                     Bandarban (4,479 km²) is not only the most remote district of the country,
                     but also is the least populated (population 292,900) one.
                    [2]Bandarban (meaning the dam of monkeys), or in Marma or Arakanese language as "Rwa-daw Mro" is also known as Arvumi or the Bohmong Circle.


    </string>

</resources>
